剧情回顾...
我们得带走那个男孩
We're taking the boy.
我不会给你任何人
I'm not giving you anybody.
爸爸
Dad.
Walt
她在哪儿?
Where is she?
你是说Kate?
You mean Kate?
Kate
看看这些
Look here and here.
你看在L5的位置 病毒正在腐蚀脊椎
You can see it's eroding into the spinal artery in the L5 area.
外加硬脑膜外的生长
Plus all this extradural growth.
我很诧异 居然没有引起持久性缺血
I'm surprised it hasn't caused permanent ischemia.
他说  你们没必要窃窃私语
He says you don't need to talk in whispers.
他知道没有治愈的机会了
He knows he doesn't have a chance.
你父亲很直率
Your father appreciates candour.
我们都是
We both do.
好吧  告诉他  真的很抱歉
Well, then tell him I'm very sorry,
但是我们不会给他进行手术
but he's not a candidate for surgery.
肿瘤位于脊柱上
The way the tumour is situated on the spine,
是不可能切除的
it's not possible to remove it.
他想知道你为什么不试一下
He wants to know why you won't try.
因为你父亲需要的
Because what your father is looking for
不是外科手术
is not a surgical procedure.
他需要的是奇迹
What he is looking for is a miracle.
他说"我并不是冲着你来的  先生
He said, "I did not come all this way for you, sir.
我是冲着他来的"
I came for him."
Busoni小姐...我...
Ms Busoni...I...
你曾治愈过一个脊柱粉碎的女人
You fixed a woman with a crushed spinal column.
一个不可能的手术
An impossible surgery.
她现在可以走路了吧?
And now she walks, yes?
在我来这之前 我参考过许多医学期刊
I consulted many medical journals before making this trip.
你要知道  那是完全不同的病例
Then you know it was a very different case
完全不一样的情况
under different circumstances.
是个奇迹  对吧?
But a miracle, right?
听着  我父亲说的每一句话
Look, Everything that my father's saying,
风险  不可能性  他说的一点没错
the risks, the unlikelihood, he's absolutely right.
但你是否愿意试一下?
But will you try?
接下来的几周我来安排
I'll have to admit him in the next couple of weeks,
给他做一些测试
run some tests.
声明: 本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
欢迎访问官方论坛  www.YYeTs.net 在线观看 剧情讨论 学习交流
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：Singa校对：雯雯  七色九天
后期：xyz 双语制作：DrunkBat
========== 字幕总监制：七色九天 ==========
Locke?
John
别动
Stay in there.
-别动...  -Michael  你...
-Stay in there.  -Michael, What are you...
别动  Jack
Stay in there, Jack.
不管发生了什么...
Whatever's going on...
听着  我去找我的儿子
Look, I'm going after my son.
没人能阻止我 知道吗?
And nobody is going to stop me, okay?
那是我的权力  是一个父亲的权力
That is my right. That is a father's right.
呆在那儿
Get in the damn room!
你真打算向我开枪 Micheal?
You gonna shoot me, Micheal?
不  但是我会打那台该死的电脑
No. But I'll shoot your damn computer.
事情不是你想的那样
That thing is not what you think it is anyway.
你不会明白的
You don't understand, man.
你不会知道的 现在马上进去
You don't have any idea. Now get in there.
Michael! Michael  听着 我们可以一起去找  好吗?
Michael! Michael, listen, We can do this together, okay?
-我跟你一起去  -不  我现在就去找
-I'll come with you.  -No. I have to do it. Now.
我一个人去
And I have to do it alone.
怎么回事?
What happened?
Michael把你打晕了
Michael knocked you out.
看这里
Look over here.
他为什么?
Why would he?
他去找Walt了
He went after Walt.
觉得恶心
You feel nauseated,
不舒服?
sick?
不  我没事
No. I'm Okay.
很好  拉我一下
Good. Give me a boost up.
没用的
It's no use.
上锁了
I bolted it shut from the inside.
你做了什么?
You did what?
没别的办法
No point changing the combination
除非你能从通风口钻出去
if you can get in through the air vent.
真是好主意  John
That's really good thinking, John.
想告诉我为什么让Micheal进来?
You want to tell me why you let Michael in here?
他...
He...
他要把枪
He wanted a gun.
要练习射击
For shooting practice.
射击练习
Shooting practice.
那个按键
The button.
我晕了多久?
How long was I out?
大约20分钟
About 20 minutes.
接下来的4小时是我们的班
We're on shift for the next four hours.
没有人会下来的
There's nobody coming down here.
对  我知道
Yeah, I know.
我们只能寄希望Sawyer会下来换绷带
We better hope Sawyer shows up to get his Band-Aid changed.
早上好
Morning.
刚才是你向我丢香蕉?
Did you just throw a banana at me?
因为找不到石头
Couldn't find any rocks.
叫醒人的方法还有很多  小妞
There are nicer ways to wake a man up, Freckles.
走吧 该去换绷带了
Come on. It's time to get your bandages changed.
为什么你不帮我换?
Why can't you do it for me?
因为我不是你的护士
Because I'm not your nurse.
Jack那里有绷带
And Jack's got the bandages.
他当然有
Of course he does.
能拉我一把吗?
You want to give me a hand?
谢了
Thanks.
走吧
Come on.
这地方让我毛骨悚然
This place still creeps me out.
你会习惯的
You'll get used to it.
人呢?
Where is everybody?
Jack?  John?
-也许他们出去吃冰淇淋了  -在这里
-Maybe they went out for ice cream.  -In here.
Jack?
在这里  军械库里
In here. In the armoury.
Michael把我们锁里面了
Michael locked us in here.
他说什么?
What did he say?
我来
I got it.
希望你们知道密码
Hope you got the combo, Doctor.
顺时针转3圈到25
Right three times to 25.
25  搞定
25, got it.
逆时针转2圈到29
Left two times to 29.
顺时针1圈到40
Right once to 40.
你们好 伙计们
Howdy, boys.
你想干嘛  Jack?
What are you doing, Jack?
我们去找他
We're going after him.
嘿  什么
Hey, what?
怎么回事?
What happened?
Michael去找Walt了
Michael went after Walt.
去找Walt?
Went after Walt?
他用枪指着我
Held a gun on me,
把我们关在里面
put us both in there,
然后去找Walt了
and went after Walt.
你要干嘛?
What're you doing?
你觉得呢?
What does it look like?
和你们一起去
I'm coming with you.
你还需要抗生素
You're still on antibiotics.
那就更要跟着我的医生一起了
It's a good thing I'm travelling with my doctor then.
他怎么样?
How is he?
我还以为你回家了呢
I thought you'd gone home.
我住在旅馆
My home is a hotel room.
我更喜欢病房
I like it more here.
那你应该找个更好的旅馆
I think you need to find a better hotel.
你还没回答我的问题
You didn't answer my question.
他的情况不是很乐观
His counts aren't where I'd like them to be.
你已经测试了一个月了 Jack
You've been doing tests for a month now, Jack.
我得很细心
I'm thorough.
坦白跟你讲
I have a confession to make.
我不相信奇迹
I don't believe in miracles.
对  也许我也不太相信
Yeah. Guess I'm not too sure about them, either.
我敢说你妻子并不这么认为
I bet your wife feels differently.
你妻子就是你治愈的那个女人  对吧?
Your wife, she is the woman you fixed, isn't she?
对
Yes.
我也很细心
I'm thorough, too.
她一定很特别 会允许你熬夜工作到凌晨4点30
She must be very special person to let you work until 4:30 in the morning.
我完全忘了时间了...
I completely lost track...
我得...我先走了行吗?
I gotta... Will you excuse me?
当然
Of course. Go.
Jack
谢谢
Thank you.
应该的
Of course.
-晚安  -晚安
-Good night.  -Good night.
嘿
Hey.
他怎样了?
How is he?
嘿  抱歉把你吵醒了
Hey. Sorry to wake you.
我总要起床的
I gotta get up anyway.
他怎么样了?
So, how is he?
还是老样子
About the same.
Sarah  我很抱歉  我的意思是...
Sarah, I'm sorry. I meant to...
我本来想...
I just got...
我...
I...
那是创造奇迹的代价
That's the price of being a miracle worker.
你要去哪?
Where you going?
我先去健身
I gotta go to the gym.
然后去改论文
Then I got some papers to grade.
在了解之前  我什么都不想说
I didn't wanna say anything until I knew either way,
但是...
but...
我的例假还没来  所以我做了验孕
I was late, so I got a pregnancy test.
别担心  没怀上
Don't worry. It was negative.
你...
Do you...
你想谈谈吗?
Do you wanna talk about it?
谈什么?
What's to talk about?
Sarah  我...
Sarah, I...
一会儿见  Jack
See you later, Jack.
怎么?
Well?
我不能说这绝对是Michael的
I can't say it's definitely Michael's,
但是看起来像他的鞋印
but it looks like his boot print.
这里也有一个
There's one over here, too.
看起来是他的踪迹
That sounds like a trail.
有枪给我吗?
You got a gun for me?
你别跟来
You're not coming.
-什么?    -你别跟来
-Excuse me?    -You're not coming.
得有人留下来管那个按键
Someone has to take care of the button.
那为什么是我?
So, why should that person be me?
-我可以追踪  拿枪...  -你别跟来
-I can track, carry a gun...  -You're not coming.
你留下
You're staying.
可以么?
All right?
我们走
Let's go.
她对你怎么了?
What did she do to you?
什么?
What?
Kate  她做了什么?
Kate. What'd she do?
她什么都没做
She didn't do anything.
好吧  那你朝她大吼
Right. Yelling at her
就因为她想帮助找回Mike这件事很有意义?
because she wanted to help get Mike makes a lot of sense.
你为什么不回去 看看我是否伤了她的心?
Why don't you go back and see if I hurt her feelings?
我正想说呢
I'm just saying.
恩  我知道
Yeah, I know.
你爱她
You love her.
你说什么?
What'd you say?
什么?
What?
是你回来的那条路么?
Does any of this look familiar from when you were coming back?
对  这是我最喜欢的叶子
Yeah. There's my favourite leaf.
我怎能忘记这地方?
How could I forget this place?
怎么了?
What's wrong?
当你们穿过这个岛 这边的海是哪个方向?
When you came across the island, what side was the ocean on?
你从东边来 Michael朝北走
You came from the east. Michael's heading north.
你到底要说什么?
What the hell's that supposed to mean?
就是说他不会回到你们来的那地方去
That means he's not going back to where you came from.
他往其他方向走了
He's heading somewhere else.
今天太阳很大
我不要帽子
我知道
戴着它
我觉得出事了
好啊  Hurley
Hello, Hurley.
帽子不错  伙计
Cool hat, dude.
Kate还好吧?
Is Kate all right?
呃..是呀
Uh...Yeah.
我猜Michael跑了
I guess Michael took off.
他说什么了?
你说什么  他跑了?
What do you mean, he took off?
他偷了一些枪独自出去了
He stole some guns and he went all commando.
据说他是去找Walt
Said he was going after Walt.
等会见  伙计  得去舱里了
Later, dudes. Gotta get to the hatch.
你在干嘛?
他说他们刚走
如果快的话我还能追上...
你哪里都不能去
别走
别离开我
当你还在竹筏上时...
知道我有多担心吗?
一想到你生死未卜
我都快要疯掉了
我不想再那样了
Micheal是我朋友
我是你妻子
医生
Doctor.
走慢点行吧?
You wanna slow down?
休息一会吧?
Take a break a minute?
好主意
Good idea.
他还在往北走?
He still heading north?
对
Yep.
你觉得他迷路了?
You think he's lost?
不会
Doesn't seem to be.
足迹像公路一样笔直
Trail's as straight as the interstate.
是一个有方向感的人走的路
The path of a man who knows where he's going.
你要怎么做  Jack?
Where are you going, Jack?
什么?
What?
如果我们赶上了Micheal
Let's say we catch up with him, Micheal.
你要怎么做?
What are you gonna do?
我要把他带回来
I'm gonna bring him back.
万一他不想回来呢?
What if he doesn't wanna come back?
我会说服他回来
I'll talk him into coming back.
这是他第二次去找Walt  而且把我打晕了
This is the second time he's gone after Walt. He knocked me out.
他把我们都关起来了
He locked us both up.
直觉告诉我他不会听你说理
Something tells me he might be past listening to reason.
什么  你觉得我们应该随他去
What, you think we should just let him go?
不管他了?
Write him off?
我们有什么资格去告诉别人该做什么不该做什么?
Who are we to tell anyone what they can or can't do?
现在回去还来得及
It's not too late to go back.
瘤在扩散
The tumour's aggressive,
但是你父亲还可以 正常生活至少一年
but your father could lead a normal life for at least another year.
回去? 回哪里? 家?
Go back? Go back where? Home?
你改变主意了吗  Jack?
Have you changed your mind, Jack?
不  不
No. No.
这就行了?
Is that it?
即使你没成功
Even if you don't succeed,
至少给了我们机会
you're giving us a chance.
我们不敢奢望什么
That's all we wanted.
手术前  我还会出来跟你确认一下
I'll come out and check on you before I scrub in.
好的
Okay.
我妨碍你们说话了吗?
Am I interrupting?
没  我正准备走
No, I was just leaving.
明早见
I'll see you in the morning.
检查报告要你签字
I.T.R. reports need to be signed by you as chief resident.
什么?
What?
小心
Careful.
做事要有限度 儿子 你知道的
There's a line, Son. You know it's there.
如果超过了限度...
Pretending it's not
就会酿成大错
that would be a mistake.
我猜你应该知道
Guess you would know.
对一些人来说可能没问题  Jack
It may be okay for some people, Jack
但你不是
but not for you.
确定Mike往这里走?
You sure Mike went this way?
为什么这样问?
Why do you ask?
我不知道  清道夫先生
I don't know, Mr Clean.
或许我应该去爬维苏威山
I probably would have gone around Mount Vesuvius.
你为什么选那个名字?
Why'd you pick that name?
不明显吗?
Ain't it obvious?
再加上耳环和拖把就行了
All you need's an earring and a mop.
不 你的名字 为什么选名叫"Sawyer"?
No. Your name. Why did you pick Sawyer?
什么叫"选"?
What do you mean, "pick"?
在人员调查后  Hurley给了我旅客名单
After the census, Hurley gave me the flight manifest.
你叫James  对吧?
Your name is James, right?
James Ford
那又怎样?
What's it to you?
真是选了个有趣的名字
Just an interesting name to choose, is all.
从谁那里参考来的?
Who'd you get it from?
谁说我的名字是从别人那里来的?
Who says I got it from anybody?
Michael
Jack  蹲下
Jack, get down.
-Michael    -Jack!
Jack
Michael
什么?
What?
他就在附近
He's close.
对 如果他都朝某人开枪了 你还想他会回来?
Yeah, and if he was shooting at someone. You want them coming back?
对我来说 是的
Personally, hell, yeah.
你说这些人两天前穿过这个岛
You said these people were two days away across the island.
对  他们从我们营地不到一公里处带走了Cindy
Yeah, and they took Cindy less than a mile from our camp.
过来看看
Over here.
空弹壳
Shell casings.
-几发?  -3发  Michael的
-How many?   -Three. Michael's.
你们聋了?  我听到至少7声
You boys deaf? I heard at least seven shots.
你也听到了对吧 Daniel Boone  你听到几声?
You heard them, Daniel Boone. What's your count?
对  差不多7声
Yeah. Seven sounds about right.
天快黑了
It's getting dark.
Mike会往哪去?
Which way did Mike go?
怎么了?
What?
你出来是找Michael
You out here for Michael,
还是为了来报复那次枪击?
or just payback for getting shot?
那你来这儿干嘛?
Why are you out here, Doctor?
你有你的想法
You got your reasons,
我也有我的
and I got mine.
Jack
-我都快成功了  -我知道  孩子
-I had it.  -I know, Son.
要成了  要成了  都快成功了
I got it! I got it all. I mean, I had it!
他是个生病的老人 已经在台上躺了7个半小时了
He was a sick old man on a table for seven and a half hours.
他心脏不跳了  这不是谁的错
His heart gave out. It's nobody's fault.
必须告诉她
I've got to go tell her.
是的 我已经说了
Yeah, well, I've already done that.
免得你忘记  我还是外科主任
Lest you forget, I am still chief of surgery.
她在哪?
Where is she?
-也许你该回家去  -她在哪?
-Maybe you should go home.  -Where is she?
她走了
She's gone.
Jack...
回家去吧
Go home.
Jack?
Gabriela
我父亲告诉我 你已经走了
My father told me that you'd gone.
-我 呃...    -谢谢
-I, uh...   -Thank you.
感谢你的尝试
Thank you for trying.
Gabriela...
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
很抱歉  很抱歉我没能...
I'm so sorry that I couldn't...
没事的
It's okay.
我...
I...
I'm...
我不能这样
I can't.
你说什么?  你跟丢了?
What do you mean, you lost it?
他是人  不是野猪  他要更狡猾一些
He's a man, not a boar. His sign's more subtle.
我需要灯光指引
I need light to follow him.
给你
Here.
火把
Light.
-我觉得最好还是回去    -什么?
-I think we'd better head back.  -What?
去找踪迹  John
Just find the trail, John.
-我找不到线索了    -你不是找不到
-I've lost the trail.    -You don't just lose a trail.
你是不想找他
You just don't want to find him.
对  说得对  Jack
Yeah, that's right, Jack.
我顺着枪声穿越丛林
I've been running through the jungle toward the sound of gunfire
而我不在乎Micheal
because I don't care about Michael.
别想改变我的想法  John
Don't turn around on me, John.
你不会把他带回去的 你自己很清楚
You won't get him to come back, and you know it!
如果我们回去会发生什么?
You know what happens if we just turn around and go back?
我们就再也见不到他了
We're never gonna see him again.
这取决于我们...
And that's gonna be on us...
取决于你和我
On you and on me.
你说的很对  Jack
You're exactly right, Jack.
但是如果我是你
But if I were you,
我会听Locke先生的
I'd listen to Mr Locke.
你是谁?
Who are you?
在竹筏上朝我开枪的那个婊子养的
He's the son of a bitch that shot me on the raft.
为什么不把枪放下?
Why don't you point the gun down?
也许你们最好把两手放好
Probably be best if we just keep our hands at our sides, gentlemen.
Michael在哪?
Where's Michael?
别担心Michael
Don't worry about Michael.
他不会找到我们的
He's not gonna find us.
你想怎样?
What do you want?
为什么不生火呢  John?
Why don't you build us a fire, John?
是时候我们谈谈了
I think it's time we all had a talk.
Geronimo Jackson?
恩
Huh.
作为一个音乐方面的行家
As an expert in all things musical,
我从没听说过这些家伙  真不应该
I never heard of these guys, shocking as that may be.
Geronimo Jackson
Geronimo Jackson?
这个看起来不错
This looks sweet.
我们听听吧
Let's give her a rip.
好
Yeah.
你觉得那个Libby背后发生过什么故事?
So, what do you think is the story with that Libby chick?
故事?
The story?
她挺可爱的  是吧?
She's kind of cute, right?
你知道就是"我被其他人恐吓了40天"的那种
You know, in a "I've been terrorized by the Others for 40 days" kind of way.
是啊  是的
Yeah, there is that.
我觉得我跟她有希望
I think I have a chance with her.
我说  这是个经典的以荒岛为背景的故事
I mean, it's the classic desert-island scenario.
如果让我选
If I ever had a shot,
就选这个
this is it.
你觉得Claire已经开始想我了么?
You think Claire's missed me yet?
伙计  都烦了一天了
Dude, it's been a day.
这音乐很郁闷
This music is quite depressing.
我们可以换一张  伙计
We can change it, dude.
你听过Geronimo Jackson么?
You ever hear of Geronimo Jackson?
恐怕没有 Jack和Locke去哪儿了?
I'm afraid not. Where is Jack and Locke?
他们去找Michael了
They went after Michael.
-Michael?  -是啊  他又去找Walt了
-Michael?  -Yeah, he's run after Walt again.
大家都去了想把他找回来
Everyone's gone to bring him back.
大家指谁?
Who's everyone?
大家是Jack  Sawyer  Locke
Everyone...Jack, Sawyer, Locke.
还有Kate
And Kate.
坐下  Jack  没人会伤害你的
Just sit down, Jack. Nobody's gonna hurt you.
我为了和平而来
I come in peace.
你怎么知道我们的名字?
How do you know our names?
你带走了Walt
You took Walt.
Walt很好
Walt's fine.
他是个很特别的孩子
He's a very special boy.
听着  你说过你想谈谈
Look, you said you wanted to talk.
那就谈谈
Talk.
让我问问你 你来到这个岛上多久了?
Let me ask you this, how long you been here on the island?
50天
Fifty days.
50天  都快两个月了
Fifty days? That's, what almost two whole months.
告诉我
Tell me,
你第一次去别人家时
you go over a man's house for the first time,
你会脱掉鞋子吗
do you take off your shoes?
你会把脚搁在他的咖啡桌上吗
Do you put your feet up on his coffee table,
你会走进厨房  吃不属于你的食物
do you walk in the kitchen, eat food that doesn't belong to you,
你会打开你无权打开的门  闯进他人房间吗?
open the door to rooms you got no business opening?
你知道 有位比在坐各位都聪明的人说过
You know, somebody a whole lot smarter than anybody here once said,
"人类自诞生之日起
"Since the dawn of our species,
就被赋予了好奇之心"
man has been blessed with curiosity."
你知道另一个关于好奇心的事吗  Jack?
You know the other one about curiosity, don't you, Jack?
这不是你们的岛
This is not your island.
这是我们的岛
This is our island.
你们之所以能生存下来
And the only reason you're living on it
是因为我们让你们生存
is because we let you live on it.
我不相信你
I don't believe you.
你不相信什么?
You don't believe what?
我认为你们只有一个人一把枪
I think you got one guy with a gun.
我认为我们的人比你的人多
I think there's more of us than there are of you.
我认为你如果真有实力
I think if you had any real strength,
你就不用派间谍了
you wouldn't have had to send a spy.
Ethan
这是个有趣的理论
That's an interesting theory.
点火
Light them up.
我们有些误会  Jack...
We got a misunderstanding, Jack...
你的人  我的人
Your people, my people.
所以听好了
So listen carefully.
这儿有条线
Right here, there's a line.
一旦你跨过了这条线
You cross that line,
我们将会从误会升级到
we go from misunderstanding to
更可怕的程度
something else.
现在把你的武器给我  回去吧
Now give me your weapons, turn around,
回你们那儿去
and go home.
不
No.
-Jack  或许...  -不
-Jack, maybe...  -No!
我本不希望这样
I hoped it wouldn't come to this.
把她带出来  Alex
Bring her out, Alex.
她跟着你们
She was following you.
就像我说的...
Like I said...
好奇心的事
curiosity.
别动
Don't.
Jack  你现在要做出决定
Jack, the decision you gotta make right now is this.
你是眼睁睁看着我当你面打死这个女人
Can you live with the fact that I shot this woman right in front of you,
还是为救她 放弃掉 转身回去
and you could've saved her life by giving up and going home?
现在把你的枪给我
Now you gonna give me your guns,
回你们的地方去
turn around, and walk away.
全凭你的主意  Jack
It's your call, Jack.
-要是你动她一根指头我就...  -闭嘴
-If you touched a hair on her head, I'll...  -Shut up.
我数三下
I'm going to count to three.
一
One.
二
Two.
停下
Stop.
还有他们
Now them.
另一把也给我
Give me the other one, too.
咱俩没完  Zeke
You and me ain't done, Zeke.
Jack...我...
Jack...I...
你没事吧?
You all right?
没事
Yeah.
为什么一个人坐在这里?
我睡不着
他们回来了吗?
还没
亲爱的
我不喜欢听别人的话做事
过去的四年里 听命行事是我全部的生活
我也讨厌那样
我懂了
我不想你那样的
我只是想帮忙  Jack
I was just trying to help, Jack.
当你叫我别去  我感觉...
When you told me not to go, I just...
我错了
I made a mistake.
你能不能跟我说句话?
Could you just talk to me for a second?
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
是的
Yeah.
我也很抱歉
I'm sorry, too.
怎么样了?
How did it go?
他死了
He died.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
是啊  我也是
Yeah. Me too.
谁来过了?
Who was over?
我妈
My mom.
她桥牌玩的如何?
The bridge game okay?
哦  很好  她运气正旺
Oh yeah. She's on a streak.
你  你吃过了么?
Did you..did you eat?
吃了  没  我...只是...
Yeah. No. I...it's...
已经迟了  算了
It's late. I'm fine.
我来好了
You don't have to do that.
用来治疗自己
It's therapeutic.
比找心理医生便宜
Cheaper than a shrink.
那他女儿怎么样了?
How did the daughter take it?
她叫Gabriela吧
What's her name, Gabriela?
她吻了我
She kissed me.
是的  她...
Yeah, she...
她吻了我  然后....
She kissed me and...
我也吻了她
I kissed her back.
我...
I...
我...我不知道 我不知道怎么会那样  我只是...
I... I don't know, I don't know how it happened. I just...
我错了
I made a mistake,
我犯了错  这是我的错
I made a mistake, and this is my fault.
这是我的错让你和我...
It's my fault that you and me...
我很少来这里 Sarah
I haven't been here, Sarah.
我是说...
I mean...
我们甚至都不说话了
We don't even talk anymore.
我恨我们之间发生的事
I hate what's happening to us, and
我答应你Sarah 事情会好起来的  我会...
I promise you that things are gonna be different.
我会...我会少工作
I'm gonna...I'm gonna work less.
多陪你
I'm gonna be here for you.
好吗?  我会解决的 我们会像过去一样
Okay? I'm gonna fix this. We're gonna go back to the way things were.
我会解决的  我会解决的
I'm gonna fix this. I'm gonna fix this.
Jack
我要离开你了
I'm leaving you.
什么?
What?
我已经准备离开你了
I was already leaving you.
我妈来这就是为了帮我收拾的
That's why my mother was here. She was helping me pack.
我已经在跟别人约会了
I've been seeing someone.
别的人
Someone else.
我必须这样...
I have to...
我不能留下来了
I can't stay.
Sarah...
你...
You...
你总会有事情需要解决
You will always need something to fix.
再见
Goodbye.
再见  James
See you, James.
别为难自己  小妞
Don't beat yourself up, Freckles.
如果他让我留下来  我也会跟你一样做的
If he'd told me to stay behind, I'd have done the same thing.
你好  怎么了?
Oh. Hello. What's the matter?
你的小脚怎么了?
What's the matter with the little squirt?
那是谁啊?
Who's that?
你不喜欢的Johnny叔叔?
You don't like old Uncle Johnny?
你的玩具呢?
What is he doing to your toy?
他在干什么?
What is he doing?
嘿  走开
Hey, go away.
我自己都填不饱肚子了
I barely have enough food to feed myself.
来  给你  去吧
Here. Get that. Go!
看来你找到了个新朋友
I see you found a new friend.
有进步
Progress.
听说你去找Michael了
I hear you were out looking for Michael.
是啊
Yeah.
他又去找他的孩子了?
He ran off looking for his kid again?
你能做的只有这么多了
Not much you can do about that then.
你杀了他们其中一个是真的吗?
Is it true that you killed one of them?
谁的其中一个?
One of who?
其他人
Them.
Sayid告诉我你是个警察
Sayid tells me that you're a cop.
我曾经是个警察
I was a cop.
能问你点事吗?
Can I ask you something?
说
Shoot.
你认为训练一支军队要多久?
How long would it take to train an army?
==============|  YYeTs字幕组招募启示  |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国)  双语字幕校正   时间轴调整
英语翻译   欧美影视新闻翻译  影视评论  论坛版主  美工人员
服务器提供者  发布宣传  联系地址：www.YYeTs.com
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报酬 ====